motiveinteractive.com 2018-03-25

# Privacy Policy

### Motive Interactive Website Privacy Policy

* * *

Thank you for your interest in Motive Interactive, Inc. (referred to herein as “Motive Interactive,” “we” or “us”) and our website located at http://new.motiveinteractive.com (the “Site”). We are pleased to provide this privacy policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use Personal Information (defined below) about visitors to the Site. By using this Site, you consent to the following terms. 

What We Collect 

The data that we regularly collect about visitors to our Site (e.g., IP address, browser type, pages accessed, duration of visit, etc.) does not necessarily enable us to personally identify you, and that is not our intention. We do collect personally identifiable information about you (“Personal Information”), including without limitation, your name, billing address, mailing address, email address, gender, how you like to receive email messages, age, interests, and credit card information (if needed to process an order placed by you), but only if you voluntarily provide it to us, for example, by registering, placing an order, participating in one of our programs and/or requesting information from us. Further, if you communicate with us, we may keep all such correspondence as part of your user account. 

### Cookies

To facilitate your use of the Site, Motive Interactive uses “cookies.” A cookie is a small amount of data that Motive Interactive’s servers transfer to your browser and that only Motive Interactive’s servers can read. When you log onto the Site, the cookie file captures your username, unique session identifier number and other session data to enable you to traverse through this website’s various screens without having to authenticate yourself at each new screen. Motive Interactive uses cookies to understand general information on site traffic trends such as most frequently visited pages. If you do not wish to utilize cookies, you may disable or delete them from within your Internet browser application by accessing the security or privacy settings. You may, however, be required to have cookies enabled to access certain portions of the Site or participate in our programs. 

### Use of Information

General Uses
     Motive Interactive uses your Personal Information primarily to provide products and services that you have requested, to send promotional information, and to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems. Personal Information is also used to verify your authority to access the Site. Motive Interactive may also use any information you have entered into the Site as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the Site. 
Promotional Uses
     Motive Interactive may also store and use your Personal Information for our own mailing and database purposes, and to send you information related to your interest areas and from other pre- screened companies that have products that we believe may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt-out of having your information used for marketing purposes by Motive Interactive, please see the “How to Opt-Out” section below for instructions on how to inform us of this choice. 

### Disclosure of Information

Motive Interactive uses certain third party vendors (e.g., data storage and processing facilities) to assist us in providing our products and services. Motive Interactive may transfer your Personal Information to such vendors for their use as necessary to fulfill their contracts with Motive Interactive. We may also disclose your Personal Information as we believe is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others. Your Personal Information may also be disclosed upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of our stock or assets in the line of business to which this privacy policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization. We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties that we believe may be of interest to you for their own marketing purposes, including without limitation, bringing you select retail opportunities via direct mail, email and telemarketing. Motive Interactive may also use trusted third party business partners (“Partners”) to host short surveys or offer forms on the Motive Interactive Site and affiliated sites. When you select an offer, we may pre-populate Personal Information in these forms to make it easier for you to get information about various special offers and services. If you agree to participate in an offer hosted by Motive Interactive or our Partners, your Personal Information included in the form will be transmitted to the appropriate advertiser referenced in the survey or offer. 

### How to Opt-Out

     If you do not wish your information shared with third parties by Motive Interactive for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such disclosure by notifying Motive Interactive using the contact information provided below. Upon opting-out, Motive Interactive will not make further disclosures of your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes. Please allow up to seven (7) business days to be completely opted-out from such use. Keep in mind that if you take advantage of an offer from a Motive Interactive business partner, they may independently wish to send offers to you. In the event that you wish to opt-out of receiving future offers from these third parties, you must contact them directly to make such a request. 
  
     Should you wish to opt out of seeing personalized ads, please follow the links below for general instructions on how you can reset your Adertising IDs (AAID/IDFA) for both Android and iOS devices. 
  
     Mobile In-App Opt Out (Android)  
  
     Mobile In-App Opt Out (iOS)  

### How You Can Change, Correct and Update Your Information

You may change certain of your Personal Information we have on file for you at any time by visiting the Edit My Preferences page on the Site and making your desired changes. 

### Links

In connection with the Site, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that these third parties’ policies with respect to privacy, and not the Motive Interactive privacy policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with these third parties. Motive Interactive does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of such third party websites, including those that are framed within the Site. 

### Security

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed, despite these efforts. 

### No Collection of Information From Children

You must be 18 years of age or older to access the Site. Motive Interactive has no interest in collecting information people under 18 years of age. 

### Policy Changes

Motive Interactive reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on the Site. We encourage you to review this privacy policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy. In the event that we make a change to this Privacy Policy that we believe is material in nature, we will notify you of such change using the email address that you have provided to us, and give you an opportunity to opt-out of such changes. 

### Questions?

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at: 

Address
     Motive Interactive, Inc. 6020 Cornerstone Court West Ste. 280 San Diego, California 92121 
Phone
    858-677-0792
Email
    privacy@motiveinteractive.com
